A Guide to the Papers of Francis L. Berkeley Jr. 1935-2005
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I Professional Papers
  - 1948-1951 E. Graham Roberts (Box-folder 6:13)
  - 1975-1976 Rotunda Restoration (Box-folder 6:14)
  - 1974-1975 Larry Sabato (Box-folder 6:15)
  - 1961 Duncan Sandy (Box-folder 6:16)
  - 1960-1997 Edgar F. Shannon (Box-folder 6:17)
  - 1954-1955 Hisham Shawi (Box-folder 6:18)
  - 1962-1995 University Press of Virginia (Box-folder 6:19)
  - 1957-1982 Joseph L. Vaughan (Box-folder 6:20)
  - 1973 Edward Younger (Box-folder 6:21)
- Series II Personal Papers
  - 1963-1995 Correspondence between Francis L. Berkeley, Jr. and Helen (Box-folder 7:1)
  - 1993-1994 Death of Helen S. Berkeley (Box-folder 7:2)
  - 1954 April 8 Estate of Elizabeth Sutherland (Box-folder 7:3)
  - 1954-1962 Estate of George Edward Smith (Box-folder 7:4)
  - 1949-1961 Financial and Legal Papers (Box-folder 7:5)
  - 1971-1988 Financial and Legal Papers (Box-folder 7:6)
  - 1989-1994 Financial and Legal Papers (Box-folder 7:7)
  - 1995-2001 Financial and Legal Papers (Box-folder 7:8)
  - 1975-1992 Medical Correspondence (Box-folder 7:9)
  - n.d. Membership and identification cards (Box-folder 7:10)
  - n.d. miscellaneous poem (Box-folder 7:11)
  - 1961;1974-2002 Personal correspondence (Box-folder 7:12)
  - n.d.;1996 Personal correspondence and verses of Cynthia Sabatini (Box-folder 8:1)
  - 1969-1995 Personal correspondence of Ruari and Antonia McClean (Box-folder 8:2)
  - n.d. Personal Photographs (Box-folder 8:3)
  - 1989-1994 Pocket calendar diaries (Box-folder 8:4)
  - 1995-1999 Pocket claendar diaries (Box-folder 8:5)
  - 1977-1984 Political correspondence (Box-folder 8:6)
  - 1975-1981 Politics: Oceanic Education Foundation (Box-folder 8:7)
  - 1976 Red Hill School fiftieth re-union (Box-folder 8:8)
  - 1972-1975 Wintergreen house remodeling (Box-folder 8:9)
- Series III U.S. Naval Papers
  - 1945-1946 Bomb Disposal Branch (Box-folder 9:1)
  - 1947-1973 Navy Advisory Committee (Box-folder 9:2)
  - 1974-1976 Navy Advisory Committee (Box-folder 9:3)
  - 1977-1978 Navy Advisory Committee (Box-folder 9:4)
  - 1979-1981 Navy Advisory Committee (Box-folder 9:5)
  - 1982-1983 Navy Advisory Committee (Box-folder 9:6)
  - 1942-1971 Navy forms and correspondence (Box-folder 9:7)
  - 1966-1973 Navy photographs (Box-folder 9:8)
  - n.d. Artifacts including naval insignia and jewelry
  - 1971-1975 Navy Retirement (Box-folder 9:9)
- Series IV Travel
  - n.d. Brochures for Travel (Box-folder 10:1)
  - 1979-1980 Cruise Lines (Box-folder 10:2)
  - 1982-1987 Florida (Box-folder 10:3)
  - 1961 Insurance for Travel (Box-folder 10:4)
  - 1980 Italy (Box-folder 10:5)
  - 1977-1978 Italy-Sorrento (Box-folder 10:6)
  - 1981-1982 Jamaica (Box-folder 10:7)
  - 1971;1980 London (Box-folder 10:8)
  - 1981;1984 London (Box-folder 10:9)
  - 1979-1980 Mexico (Box-folder 10:10)
  - 1974;1980 New York City (Box-folder 10:11)
  - 1975 Passports and vaccinations (Box-folder 10:12)
  - 1975 Russia (Box-folder 10:13)
  - 1981 Spain and Canary Islands (Box-folder 10:14)
  - 1974-1975 South America (Box-folder 10:15)
  - 1975-1983 Virginia and South Carolina (Box-folder 10:16)
  - 1983-1984 Yugoslavia and Egypt (Box-folder 10:17)